[
  {
  "front": "愛",
  "back": "愛|あい|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "愛情",
  "back": "愛情|あい.じょう|0|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "合図",
  "back": "信號、標誌|あい.ず|1|名詞／自動三"
 },
 {
  "front": "アイスクリーム",
  "back": "冰淇淋|無|5|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "愛する",
  "back": "喜好、喜愛|あい.する|3|他動三"
 },
 {
  "front": "相手",
  "back": "對方、對手|あい.て|0|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "あいにく",
  "back": "不巧、不湊巧|無|0|副詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "アイロン",
  "back": "熨斗|無|0|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "明かり",
  "back": "亮光、光線|あ.かり|0|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "空き",
  "back": "空隙、空閒|あ.き|0|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "明らか",
  "back": "明顯的、顯然的|あき.らか|2|な形"
 },
 {
  "front": "諦める",
  "back": "死心、放棄|あきら.める|4|他動二"
 },
 {
  "front": "飽きる",
  "back": "膩、受夠|あ.きる|2|自動二"
 },
 {
  "front": "握手",
  "back": "握手|あく.しゅ|1|名詞／自動三"
 },
 {
  "front": "アクセント",
  "back": "腔調、口音|無|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "明ける",
  "back": "變亮、破曉|あ.ける|0|自動二"
 },
 {
  "front": "揚げる",
  "back": "油炸|あ.げる|0|他動二"
 },
 {
  "front": "預かる",
  "back": "收存、保管|あず.かる|3|他動一"
 },
 {
  "front": "預ける",
  "back": "寄放、委託|あず.ける|3|他動二"
 },
 {
  "front": "汗",
  "back": "和、汗水|あせ|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "与える",
  "back": "給予、贈予|あた.える|0|他動二"
 },
 {
  "front": "温める",
  "back": "使溫熱、變熱|あたた.める|4|他動二"
 },
 {
  "front": "辺り",
  "back": "附近、周圍|あた.り|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "当たり前",
  "back": "當然|あ.たり.まえ|0|な形"
 },
 {
  "front": "当たる",
  "back": "曬、照|あ.たる|0|自動一"
 },
 {
  "front": "あちこち",
  "back": "這裡那裏、到處|無|2|代名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "扱う",
  "back": "處理、經營|あつか.う|0|他動一"
 },
 {
  "front": "あっという間に",
  "back": "剎那間|あっという.ま.に|1|副詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "集まり",
  "back": "集合、集會、會合|あつ.まり|3|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "当てる",
  "back": "碰撞、觸打|あ.てる|0|他動二"
 },
 {
  "front": "跡",
  "back": "痕跡、行跡|あと|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "アドバイス",
  "back": "建議|無|1|名詞／他動三"
 },
 {
  "front": "穴",
  "back": "洞、洞穴|あな|2|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "暴れる",
  "back": "橫衝直撞、亂闖|あば.れる|0|自動二"
 },
 {
  "front": "余り",
  "back": "剩餘、剩餘物|あま.り|3|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "粗い",
  "back": "粗心、粗枝大葉|あら.い|0|い形"
 },
 {
  "front": "嵐",
  "back": "暴風雨|あらし|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "新た",
  "back": "新的、新鮮的|あら.た|1|な形"
 },
 {
  "front": "あらゆる",
  "back": "所有、一切|無|3|連體"
 },
 {
  "front": "表す",
  "back": "表示、表達|あらわ.す|3|他動一"
 },
 {
  "front": "現す",
  "back": "出現、顯露|あらわ.す|3|他動一"
 },
 {
  "front": "現れる",
  "back": "出現、顯示|あらわ.れる|4|自動二"
 },
 {
  "front": "あるいは",
  "back": "或者、或許|無|2|接續"
 },
 {
  "front": "アルバム",
  "back": "相簿|無|0|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "合わせる",
  "back": "合併、調合|あ.わせる|3|自動二"
 },
 {
  "front": "案",
  "back": "計畫、方案、意見、主意|あん|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "暗記",
  "back": "記住、熟記|あん.き|0|他動三"
 },
 {
  "front": "アンケート",
  "back": "問卷調查|無|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "安定",
  "back": "安定、穩定|あん.てい|0|名詞／自動三"
 },
 {
  "front": "あんなに",
  "back": "那麼、那樣|無|0|副詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "あんまり",
  "back": "太～、過於|無|0|副詞\/な形"
 },
 {
  "front": "委員",
  "back": "委員|い.いん|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "意外",
  "back": "意外、出乎意料|い.がい|0|名詞\/な形"
 },
 {
  "front": "息",
  "back": "氣息、呼吸|いき|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "勢い",
  "back": "氣勢、權勢|いきお.い|3|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "生き物",
  "back": "生物、活的東西|い.き.もの|3|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "医師",
  "back": "醫師、醫生|い.し|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "意思",
  "back": "意思、想法|い.し|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "意志",
  "back": "意志、心意|い.し|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "維持",
  "back": "維持|い.じ|1|他動三"
 },
 {
  "front": "意識",
  "back": "意識、神智|い.しき|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "異常",
  "back": "異常、不正常|い.じょう|0|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "泉",
  "back": "泉水、泉源|いずみ|0|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "いずれ",
  "back": "哪個、哪方面|無|0|代名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "以前",
  "back": "以前、從前|い.ぜん|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "板",
  "back": "板子、(木、石)板|いた|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "偉大",
  "back": "偉大、雄偉|い.だい|0|な形"
 },
 {
  "front": "悪戯",
  "back": "開玩笑、惡作劇|いた.ずら|0|名詞／自動三"
 },
 {
  "front": "痛み",
  "back": "疼痛、悲痛|いた.み|0|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "痛める",
  "back": "弄痛、弄傷|いた.める|3|他動二"
 },
 {
  "front": "位置",
  "back": "位置、地點|い.ち|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "苺",
  "back": "草莓|いちご|0|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "一度に",
  "back": "同時|いち.ど.に|3|副詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "市場",
  "back": "市場|いち.ば|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "いつか",
  "back": "某個時候、遲早|無|1|副詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "一家",
  "back": "一家、全家|いっ.か|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "一瞬",
  "back": "瞬間、一剎那|いっ.しゅん|0|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "一生",
  "back": "一生、一輩子|いっ.しょう|0|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "一体",
  "back": "到底、究竟|いっ.たい|0|副詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "一致",
  "back": "一致、全部|いっ.ち|0|名詞／自動三"
 },
 {
  "front": "いつでも",
  "back": "無論何時、隨時|無|1|副詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "一般",
  "back": "一般、普通|いっ.ぱん|0|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "一方",
  "back": "一直、持續|いっ.ぽう|3|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "いつまでも",
  "back": "到什麼時候也、永遠|無|1|副詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "移動",
  "back": "移動、轉移|い.どう|0|名詞／自動三"
 },
 {
  "front": "従兄弟",
  "back": "堂、表 兄弟|いとこ|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "稲",
  "back": "稻子|いね|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "居眠り",
  "back": "瞌睡、打盹|い.ねむ.り|3|名詞／自動三"
 },
 {
  "front": "違反",
  "back": "違反|い.はん|0|名詞／自動三"
 },
 {
  "front": "居間",
  "back": "起居室、客廳|い.ま|2|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "今にも",
  "back": "馬上、不久|いま.にも|1|副詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "否",
  "back": "不、喔不|いや|0|感嘆"
 },
 {
  "front": "以来",
  "back": "以後、將來|い.らい|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "いらいら",
  "back": "著急、急躁|無|1|副詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "医療",
  "back": "醫療|い.りょう|1|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "岩",
  "back": "岩石|いわ|2|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "祝い",
  "back": "慶祝、賀禮|いわ.い|0|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "祝う",
  "back": "祝賀|いわ.う|2|他動一"
 },
 {
  "front": "インク",
  "back": "墨水|無|0|名詞"
 },
 {
  "front": "印刷",
  "back": "印刷|いん.さつ|0|名詞／他動三"
 }
]



